mini.com 2016-12-26

# MINI Canada

#### Personal Information Defined

Personal information is information that distinctively refers to you, such as your name, address, birth date, gender, marital status, financial information etc. Keep in mind that if you identify yourself as an employee of an organization, your name, title, business address or business telephone number would not be considered personal information.   
We collect, use and disclose personal information supplied by you for yourself and for our respective related companies and business partners (lists available on request) in order (a) to provide you with products (vehicles, parts, accessories, etc.), (b) to perform services (including Warranty, owner notifications, service reminders, etc.), (c) to improve our products and services, (d) to initiate, maintain and develop our relationship with you (including product and service information, offers, etc.), (e) to administer billing, accounting and security measures in relation to your business with us and (f) to comply with legal and regulatory requirements.

#### Collection of Personal Information

Within our website, you may be asked to provide personal information about yourself. MINI Canada will collect personal information only when you voluntarily provide it. Be assured that the personal information you provide remains strictly confidential and will be used or disclosed only for the purposes for which it was collected and will not be used or disclosed for any other reason unless you have given us consent to do so.   
We collect personal information for registration on our mailing list, for eligibility to participate in a contest, survey or promotion, or simply for informing you of upcoming events or special offers. In other areas of our website, personal information is requested in order to apply for credit in respect to a lease or finance, to register for a BMW Driver Training course or to obtain information related to pre-owned products. The personal information you provide will only be collected and used for the purposes that have been identified. In certain parts of this website where we require that you provide us with personal information such as credit card information, we will protect the security of your personal information during transmission by using industry standard encryption technology.   
We do, however, discourage you from sending any sensitive personal information (that is, credit card information) via regular email and limit such disclosure to the secure area within the website where it may be specifically requested.   
MINI Canada will not knowingly encourage children under the age of 13 to register at its website.

#### Access To Your Personal Information

At your request, we will let you know what personal information we have in our possession about you, what it is being used for, and to whom it has been disclosed. We will also provide you with access to your personal information that is in our possession, however, some exceptions may apply. We will respond to your inquiry within thirty (30) days. There may be reasonable costs associated with your request. Please direct your request to the Privacy Officer as noted above.

#### Correcting or Updating Personal Information

MINI Canada will keep the personal information in its possession accurate, complete, current and relevant, based on the most recent information available to us. If you have provided information about yourself, in order to receive emails or product mailings, and would like to modify your information, please contact one of our Customer Service Representatives by calling [ 1-800-567-2691](tel:18005672691) 1-800-567-2691³ or by mail to Customer Service, MINI Canada, 50 Ultimate Drive, Richmond Hill, ON L4S 0C8.   
³ All calls are recorded for quality assurance purposes and in accordance with our privacy policy.

#### Retention of Personal Information

MINI Canada will retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws.

#### Use of Facebook Social Plugins

One of the features of the Site is that a user has the ability to engage with social plugins (“plugins”) from the social network facebook.com, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook").   
When you access the Facebook social plugin through our Site, your browser establishes a direct connection with the Facebook servers. The content of the plugin (e.g. a “Like” button) is transferred by Facebook directly to your browser, which then integrates it into our Site. The data that your browser sends to Facebook includes your user ID, the website you're visiting, the date and time, and other browser-related information. If you are logged out of Facebook, Facebook does not receive your user ID. You can find more information about Facebook’s privacy practices at <http://www.facebook.com/policy.php>.

#### Customer Option To "Opt-Out"

You may decide that you would prefer that we do not use or disclose your personal information for MINI related marketing purposes or as otherwise noted in this Privacy Policy (excepting legal and/or contractual obligations), in particular, for some or all of the following:   
− MINI Canada Special Events and Promotions that may include notification of comparison drive events, information for golf, tennis or ski events, new car launches, brochures, etc.  
− MINI Retailer Promotions that may include retailer event information, service clinics, etc.  
− MINI Magazine Package  
− Satisfaction Surveys such as product and/or service surveys, J.D. Power, etc.  
− Marketing Surveys such as customer research surveys etc.   
If you choose to "opt-out" as outlined above, you will no longer have access to product or service information that may be of value to you. However, if you wish to "opt-out", you may do so at any time by contacting us. Please see above for contact information. Be assured that your decision to "opt-out" will not affect your business relationship with us.

#### Collection of Non-Identifiable Information

In order to allow you easy and convenient access to our websites, certain non-identifiable information is collected, as described below. We may share this information with our website providers to allow us to continually improve our websites.

#### Site Traffic Monitoring

During each and every visit to one of our websites, we will collect non-identifiable information by tracking Internet Protocol (IP) addresses on an aggregate basis. IP addresses do not track personal information about you. They simply allow us to monitor how our sites are being used and what information is being accessed. MINI Canada will use this information to ensure its websites remain useful and convenient, in order to meet and satisfy your needs.

#### "Cookies"

When a user interacts with our website, "session-cookies" are used to collect information anonymously and to track user patterns. They do not permanently record data and are only available during an active session, therefore, once a session is terminated, the "session-cookie" disappears. A session cookie is a small text file which contains a unique identification number that identifies your browser, not you personally, to our computer each time you visit our website. A session cookie can tell us which pages were visited and how often. We use this anonymous information in an effort to improve our website's usefulness to you - primarily for technical reasons, such as providing seamless navigation. If you do not want your browser to accept cookies, you can reset your browser either to notify you when you have received a cookie, or to refuse to accept them altogether. However, if you refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to use some of the features available on our websites such as personalization features.

#### Security

At MINI Canada we are committed to protecting the personal information in our possession. A number of security measures are used by MINI Canada to maintain the safety of your personal information. We have implemented security measures which include the use of: physical secure data centres and premises; internal security policies and procedures; defined internal segregation of duties; and electronic access controls such as passwords and encryption technology.

In addition, we encourage you to observe safe computing practices. It is your responsibility to keep confidential the user-ID and password that you use to register with us and not share them with anyone. If you believe that your user-ID and password have been compromised, you can change them by editing your profile at our website www.bmw.ca or by contacting MINI Canada as noted above in "Correcting or Updating Personal Information".

#### Getting Answers To Your Concerns

MINI Canada has developed policies and procedures to respond to individual complaints and questions relating to privacy. We will investigate and attempt to resolve all complaints. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days. Please be advised that there may be a reasonable cost associated with your request. Should you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy please contact our Privacy Officer as noted above.   
We welcome your comments and emails but please note that any information, including but not limited to suggestions, ideas or submissions you make through and onto any MINI website will become the exclusive property of MINI Canada.   
By visiting our websites you are agreeing to our privacy policy as outlined above. MINI Canada reserves the right to change this Policy from time to time and will provide notice of any significant changes on this website.   
© 2016 BMW Canada Inc.

#### Personal Information Defined

Personal information is information that distinctively refers to you, such as your name, address, birth date, gender, marital status, financial information etc. Keep in mind that if you identify yourself as an employee of an organization, your name, title, business address or business telephone number would not be considered personal information.   
We collect, use and disclose personal information supplied by you for yourself and for our respective related companies and business partners (lists available on request) in order (a) to provide you with products (vehicles, parts, accessories, etc.), (b) to perform services (including Warranty, owner notifications, service reminders, etc.), (c) to improve our products and services, (d) to initiate, maintain and develop our relationship with you (including product and service information, offers, etc.), (e) to administer billing, accounting and security measures in relation to your business with us and (f) to comply with legal and regulatory requirements.

#### Customer Option To "Opt-Out"

You may decide that you would prefer that we do not use or disclose your personal information for MINI related marketing purposes or as otherwise noted in this Privacy Policy (excepting legal and/or contractual obligations), in particular, for some or all of the following:   
− MINI Canada Special Events and Promotions that may include notification of comparison drive events, information for golf, tennis or ski events, new car launches, brochures, etc.  
− MINI Retailer Promotions that may include retailer event information, service clinics, etc.  
− MINI Magazine Package  
− Satisfaction Surveys such as product and/or service surveys, J.D. Power, etc.  
− Marketing Surveys such as customer research surveys etc.   
If you choose to "opt-out" as outlined above, you will no longer have access to product or service information that may be of value to you. However, if you wish to "opt-out", you may do so at any time by contacting us. Please see above for contact information. Be assured that your decision to "opt-out" will not affect your business relationship with us.

#### Collection of Personal Information

Within our website, you may be asked to provide personal information about yourself. MINI Canada will collect personal information only when you voluntarily provide it. Be assured that the personal information you provide remains strictly confidential and will be used or disclosed only for the purposes for which it was collected and will not be used or disclosed for any other reason unless you have given us consent to do so.   
We collect personal information for registration on our mailing list, for eligibility to participate in a contest, survey or promotion, or simply for informing you of upcoming events or special offers. In other areas of our website, personal information is requested in order to apply for credit in respect to a lease or finance, to register for a BMW Driver Training course or to obtain information related to pre-owned products. The personal information you provide will only be collected and used for the purposes that have been identified. In certain parts of this website where we require that you provide us with personal information such as credit card information, we will protect the security of your personal information during transmission by using industry standard encryption technology.   
We do, however, discourage you from sending any sensitive personal information (that is, credit card information) via regular email and limit such disclosure to the secure area within the website where it may be specifically requested.   
MINI Canada will not knowingly encourage children under the age of 13 to register at its website.

#### Collection of Non-Identifiable Information

In order to allow you easy and convenient access to our websites, certain non-identifiable information is collected, as described below. We may share this information with our website providers to allow us to continually improve our websites.

#### Access To Your Personal Information

At your request, we will let you know what personal information we have in our possession about you, what it is being used for, and to whom it has been disclosed. We will also provide you with access to your personal information that is in our possession, however, some exceptions may apply. We will respond to your inquiry within thirty (30) days. There may be reasonable costs associated with your request. Please direct your request to the Privacy Officer as noted above.

#### Site Traffic Monitoring

During each and every visit to one of our websites, we will collect non-identifiable information by tracking Internet Protocol (IP) addresses on an aggregate basis. IP addresses do not track personal information about you. They simply allow us to monitor how our sites are being used and what information is being accessed. MINI Canada will use this information to ensure its websites remain useful and convenient, in order to meet and satisfy your needs.

#### Correcting or Updating Personal Information

MINI Canada will keep the personal information in its possession accurate, complete, current and relevant, based on the most recent information available to us. If you have provided information about yourself, in order to receive emails or product mailings, and would like to modify your information, please contact one of our Customer Service Representatives by calling [ 1-800-567-2691](tel:18005672691) 1-800-567-2691³ or by mail to Customer Service, MINI Canada, 50 Ultimate Drive, Richmond Hill, ON L4S 0C8.   
³ All calls are recorded for quality assurance purposes and in accordance with our privacy policy.

#### "Cookies"

When a user interacts with our website, "session-cookies" are used to collect information anonymously and to track user patterns. They do not permanently record data and are only available during an active session, therefore, once a session is terminated, the "session-cookie" disappears. A session cookie is a small text file which contains a unique identification number that identifies your browser, not you personally, to our computer each time you visit our website. A session cookie can tell us which pages were visited and how often. We use this anonymous information in an effort to improve our website's usefulness to you - primarily for technical reasons, such as providing seamless navigation. If you do not want your browser to accept cookies, you can reset your browser either to notify you when you have received a cookie, or to refuse to accept them altogether. However, if you refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to use some of the features available on our websites such as personalization features.

#### Retention of Personal Information

MINI Canada will retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws.

#### Security

At MINI Canada we are committed to protecting the personal information in our possession. A number of security measures are used by MINI Canada to maintain the safety of your personal information. We have implemented security measures which include the use of: physical secure data centres and premises; internal security policies and procedures; defined internal segregation of duties; and electronic access controls such as passwords and encryption technology.

In addition, we encourage you to observe safe computing practices. It is your responsibility to keep confidential the user-ID and password that you use to register with us and not share them with anyone. If you believe that your user-ID and password have been compromised, you can change them by editing your profile at our website www.bmw.ca or by contacting MINI Canada as noted above in "Correcting or Updating Personal Information".

#### Use of Facebook Social Plugins

One of the features of the Site is that a user has the ability to engage with social plugins (“plugins”) from the social network facebook.com, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook").   
When you access the Facebook social plugin through our Site, your browser establishes a direct connection with the Facebook servers. The content of the plugin (e.g. a “Like” button) is transferred by Facebook directly to your browser, which then integrates it into our Site. The data that your browser sends to Facebook includes your user ID, the website you're visiting, the date and time, and other browser-related information. If you are logged out of Facebook, Facebook does not receive your user ID. You can find more information about Facebook’s privacy practices at <http://www.facebook.com/policy.php>.

#### Getting Answers To Your Concerns

MINI Canada has developed policies and procedures to respond to individual complaints and questions relating to privacy. We will investigate and attempt to resolve all complaints. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days. Please be advised that there may be a reasonable cost associated with your request. Should you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy please contact our Privacy Officer as noted above.   
We welcome your comments and emails but please note that any information, including but not limited to suggestions, ideas or submissions you make through and onto any MINI website will become the exclusive property of MINI Canada.   
By visiting our websites you are agreeing to our privacy policy as outlined above. MINI Canada reserves the right to change this Policy from time to time and will provide notice of any significant changes on this website.   
© 2016 BMW Canada Inc.

#### Copyright

Any visitor to these Web pages may download, copy or transmit, solely within Canada, any portion of the material in the Web pages of BMW Canada Inc. for informational and non-commercial personal purposes only. Each copy of these materials must retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained therein. The text, images, audio files, animation files, video files and any other content including customer input and their arrangement on this site are the property of BMW Canada Inc. and subject to copyright and other intellectual property protection. Furthermore, the MINI name, MINI COOPER, MINI COOPER S and logos are registered trademarks. These trademarks and other BMW names, logos and service marks may not be modified, and they may not be used, downloaded, copied or distributed in any way except as an integral part of an authorized download, copy or transmission of material in these Web pages. No license to any BMW Canada Inc. intellectual property has been granted by this site. No other use, copying or transmission, in whole or in part, of any material may be made without the express prior written permission of BMW Canada Inc. and its parent company.   
The information in these Web pages is intended for Canadian customers only and is provided "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NONINFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS. In no event shall BMW Canada Inc. be liable to any person for any special, indirect or consequential damages relating to this material.   
Any issues involving this site shall be governed by the laws of the province of Ontario and anybody using this site agrees that any lawsuit shall be litigated in provincial or federal court in Ontario.   
BMW Canada Inc. will, subject to legal requirements, determine the Model Year designation of its vehicles. The Model Year designation on any particular model may be longer or shorter than twelve months. Some vehicles pictured may contain non-Canadian equipment. Some models may be shown with optional equipment.   
All of the information contained in this site is for informational purposes only and in no way constitutes an offer to buy or sell MINI vehicles. The purchase of any MINI vehicle shall be subject to the terms and conditions of the applicable sale, lease, or financing contract.   
BMW Canada Inc. may at any time change this information by updating this posting. Visitors are bound by any such revisions and therefore should periodically visit this page to review the then-current Web site information.   
While BMW Canada Inc. makes all reasonable efforts to provide accurate information on this site, there is no guarantee or warranty of accuracy. Furthermore, we do not assume any liability for the accuracy or completeness of information presented on this site.

Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.

© 2016 BMW Canada Inc. All rights reserved.

Date: April 2016
